A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89)
1961-1991
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation.
FA479
498 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1983-1989.
Other Finding Aids
For other open RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA477 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25
Biographical/Historical note
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
As its files accumulated, the Foundation maintained a card index recording the names of institutional and individual grantees and correspondents. A microfilm copy of this index is available at the Archive Center.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Conditions Governing Access note
Material more than 20 years old is open to scholarly research, with prior archival review.
Public health administration; Public health -- Education; Philanthropy -- United States; Public health; Nursing; Philanthropy; Medical sciences; Natural history; Arts; Agriculture; Charities; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Epidemiology; Epidemics; Hospitals; Hookworm disease; Scholarships; Scarlatina -- Hospitals -- Administration; Respiratory organs -- Diseases; Public health -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Life sciences; Malaria; Humanities; Humanities -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Social sciences -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Tuberculosis; Medical care; Social sciences; Yaws; Yellow fever; Viruses -- Research; War relief; Rockefeller Foundation.
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; bulk; 1.9; 145.2 Cubic Feet; 121 standard record storage boxes - Boxes R1990-R2070, R2002A, R2002B, R2002C, R2002D, R2044A, R2076-R2110.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  Files transferred to RAC by the Rockefeller Foundation, 1983 (July 1983 and later).
  Arrangement
  Arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - International, 100
    - Films (Box R1996)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - Population - Conference, 1963 (Box R1996)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio I), 1969-1970 (Box R1996)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio II), 1971-1972 (Box R1996)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio III), 1971-1973 (Box R1996)
    - Tapes (Box R1997)
  - CIMMYT, 105
    - (CIMMYT) Administration, 1970-1979 (Box R1998)
    - Administration - Central Files, 1970-1973 1976 1978 (Box R1998)
    - Board of Directors, 1970-1979 (Box R1998)
    - Board of Directors (supplementary material - 3/26/73. Program revi[unreadable]) (Box R1999)
    - Ferroni, 1979-1982 (Box R1999)
    - Financial, 1970-1979 (Box R2000)
    - Maize Chromosomes, 1975-1977 1981-1982 (Box R2001)
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box R2001)
    - Personnel, 1971-1976 (Box R2001)
    - Publicity and Reports (supplementary material) (Box R2002)
    - Tripp, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2002)
    - CIMMYT - Turkish Wheat Project, 1966-1967, 1976; 804
      - Wheat Improvement (Box [R2002a]-[R2002d])
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Administration, 1969-1982 (Box R2003)
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Agreements, 1967-1971 1974 197[?] (Box R2003)
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Financial, 1968 1970-1982 (Box R2003)
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Organization and Planning, 1975 (Box R2003)
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Organization and Planning, 1968 (Box R2004)
      - Turkish Wheat Project - Publicity and Reports, 1968-1974 1977-1978 (Box R2004)
      - Analysis and evaluation of land reform activities in Turkey - Prof. Dr. Resat AKTAN, 1971 (Box R2002 a)
      - Land Economics - quarterly journal of Planning Housing & Public Utilities, 1957 November (Box R2002 a)
      - Incentive and welfare effects of tax structure change: The case of Turkey (Box R2002 a)
      - Buǧday Sorunu, 1974 (Box R2002 a)
      - Course handouts (Box R2002 a)
      - Marginal cost pricing (Box R2002 a)
      - Small farmer credit in Turkey - Thomas Stickley & Suha Satana, 1972 November (Box R2002 a)
      - AID spring review - Land reform in Turkey - Edwin J. Cohn, 1970 June (Box R2002 a)
      - Inputs - weed control (Box R2002 a)
      - Maps (Box R2002 a)
      - Statistics (Box R2002 a)
      - Capital & finance in Turkish agriculture - J.E. Blalock, 1969 May (Box R2002 a)
      - Corn program - Review of the Turkish corn program (Box R2002 a)
      - Oregon State University Extension service report, 1974 December (Box R2002 a)
      - Report by C. Nadir Izgin, Turkey, 1975 April (Box R2002 a)
      - Estimating value of poppy crop (Box R2002 a)
      - Reports by K.M. Kauffman - Devaluation theory, Growth models (Box R2002 a)
      - Reports by K.M. Kauffman - Conditions for viability of the Turkish economy (Box R2002 a)
      - Reports by K.M. Kauffman Markets and economic growth (Box R2002 a)
      - Technical aspects of exchange rate policy (Box R2002 a)
      - Field trip notes (Box R2002 a)
      - English-Turkish glossary of economic terms, 1972-1973 (Box R2002 a)
      - Glossary of Agricultural terms, 1961 (Box R2002 a)
      - Thoughts on integrated rural development projects in a world facing food & rural poverty crisis J.L. Fischer (Box R2002 a)
      - Marginal sector in the process of development and the Turkish case - Ilhan Tekeli, 1974 July (Box R2002 a)
      - Changes in rural structure of Turkey - Ilhan Tekeli (Box R2002 a)
      - Agricultural development project of Denizli province, 1964 July (Box R2002 a)
      - Recommendations & projections for the Turkish fertilizer industry, 1969 (Box R2002 a)
      - Economic staff papers - Olan D. Forker, 1971 (Box R2002 a)
      - Economic staff papers - Iris Kapil & Hasan Gencaga (Box R2002 a)
      - Wheat production in Turkey - Olan D. Forker, 1971 May (Box R2002 a)
      - Treatise on the timing of the agriculture price support announcement, 1970 November (Box R2002 a)
      - [Unreadable: Topraksu paper working documents A[? ] History Advisory Group Starch group) Vol. I.] (Box R2002 a)
      - Agricultural statistics in Turkish and English (Box R2002 b)
      - Agricultural structure and production, 1968 (Box R2002 b)
      - Economic and social indicators, 1972-1974 (Box R2002 b)
      - Spring review of small farmers credit, 1972 (Box R2002 b)
      - Agriculture - names (folder); includes notebooks & photo album (Box R2002 b)
      - Use of nitrogen fertilizers in wheat production under the dryland conditions of central Anatolia - C. Nadir Izgin, 19[?] (Box R2002 b)
      - End of tour report J.M. Hill, 1971 (Box R2002 b)
      - Organization & administration of agricultural in Turkey - C.T. Wilson, 1966 (Box R2002 b)
      - OECD agricultural projections - Turkey, 1968 (Box R2002 b)
      - Livestock in Turkey - D.L. Good, 1971 (Box R2002 b)
      - Back-up working documents - Luxembourg & Topraksu paper (Box R2002 b)
      - Department of Environmental Technology - Wheat project (Box R2002 b)
      - Weed control (Box R2002 b)
      - Demo program analysis (Box R2002 b)
      - Wheat - OSU/AID project (Box R2002 b)
      - Wheat - our economic project (Box R2002 b)
      - US/AID and other published reports and documents (Box R2002 c)
        - Development of Agriculture in Turkey, 1961
        - Directory of Participants, 1949-1971
        - Improving the Marketing of Fresh Fruit and Vegetables in Turkey - J.K. Samuels, 1960
        - More Wheat From Fallow Farming, 1975
        - Research, Productivity & Economic Reports on Agriculture in Turkey - L.H. Rhodes, 1969
        - Farm Mechanization in Turkey
        - Soil & Crop Management Research at the Wheat Research & Training Center - F.E. Bolton 8/73, 1973 August
        - Wheat Production Manual
        - Mass Media & Rural Development in Turkey - F.W. Frey
        - Farm Tools and Implements, 1966
        - The Turkish Administrator, A Cultural Survey, 1970
      - Fulbright Directory, 1976? (Box R2002 d)
      - Cigdem's Biblio cards (Box R2002 d)
      - Agricultural Structure and Production, 1969-1973 (Box R2002 d)
      - Census of Agricultural Sample Survey Results, 1963 (Box R2002 d)
      - Introduction of Improved Wheat Technology in Turkey by Oddvar Aresvik (Box R2002 d)
      - Assorted reports (Box R2002 d)
  - International Potato Program (IPP), 107
    - International Potato Program - Peru, 331
      - Rhoades, 1976-1982 (Box R2004)
  - CIAT, 110
    - (CIAT) Administration, 1970-1979 (Box R2005)
    - Bean Pathology, 1973-1976 (Box R2005)
    - Board of Trustees, 1970-1979 (Box R2005)
    - Financial, 1970-1979 (Box R2006)
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box R2006)
    - Pachico, 1978-1982 (Box R2007)
    - Personnel, 1966-1976 (Box R2007)
    - CIAT - Latin America, 300
      - Rice, 1966-1973 1975-1977 (Box R2007)
  - ILRAD, 112
    - (ILRAD) Financial, 1973-1975 1977-1979 (Box R2007)
    - Organization and Planning, 1965 1969-1979 (Box R2008)
    - Organization and Planning - Consultants (A-Z), 1970-1972 (Box R2008)
  - ILCA, 113
    - (ILCA) Organization and Planning, 1969-1979 (Box R2009)
  - IITA, 115
    - (IITA) Administration, 1970-1979 (Box R2009)
    - Board of Trustees, 1970-1978 (Box R2009)
    - Financial, 1970-1975 (Box R2009)
    - Financial (supplementary material) (Box R2010)
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box R2010)
    - Raintree, 1978-1982 (Box R2010)
    - Supplies and Equipment, 1965-1966 1969-1971 (Box R2010)
  - ICRISAT, 116
    - (ICRISAT) Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box R2011)
  - ICIPE, 117
    - (ICIPE), 1976-1982 (Box R2011)
    - (ICIPE), 1969-1975 (Box R2012)
  - IADS, 119
    - (IADS) Donation of Equipment, 1976 (Box R2012)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - African Dilemmas - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R1990)
    - Aging and Retirement - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Antiparasitic Drugs - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1990)
    - Artists' Education and Career Entry - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1990)
    - Child-to-child Program Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R1990)
    - China Perspectives - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Chinese Law - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box R1990)
    - CILCA - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1990)
    - Contemporary Mediterranean World Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Diarrheal Diseases and Malnutrition Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1990)
    - East-West Policy Panel Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Educational Exchanges with China Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Energy Crisis for the 80's - Conference (not held), 1980-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Folk Law Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R1990)
    - Genetics of Mosquito Disease Vectors Conference, 1979-1983 (Box R1990)
    - Health Research in the Middle East - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1991)
    - Higher Education and Foreign Student - Conference, 1977-1978 (Box R1991)
    - Insect Science in Africa - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1991)
    - International Agricultural Research Systems - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R1991)
    - Islam and the West - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1991)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Social Change Conference, 1979-1981 (Box R1991)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Chemical Safety Conference, 1978-1981 (Box R1991)
    - Neo-Confucianism in Korea - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1991)
    - Neurology and Immunology Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R1991)
    - New Energies in Developing Countries - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1991)
    - Preparing Minority Youth for the Future - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R1991)
    - Primary Health Care - Conference, 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Resource Allocation and Health Technology - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Rural Social Scientists in Africa - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Allen, S., 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Bénichou, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Becquart-Leclercq, 1978-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Blum, 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Bowers, 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Bowles, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Breen, 1980-1990 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Brumbaugh, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Bullard, 1980-1982 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Burke, J., 1980-1982 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Candlish, 1980-1982 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Cisse, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Cope, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Cox, K., 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Curry, 1981-1982 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Curtis, M., 1979-1990 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Davenport, 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - Davie, 1979-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - DeBenedetti, 1980-1981 (Box R1992)
    - Scholars - de Gennaro, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Dell, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Dittrich, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Duncan, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Elaigwa, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Erlich, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Fanger, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Fowlie, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Fraenkel-Conrat, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Frankenhaeuser, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Gelher, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Ghose, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Goffman, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Goodman, 1981-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Grob, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Grunberger, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Hall, 1980-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Halperin, 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Harper, M.C., 1979-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Holland, J., 1981-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Hunter, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Ichimura, 1980-1981 1983 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Ilan (did not go), 1980-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Jacobson, H., 1979-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Katz, J., 1980-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Kohansky, 1980-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Kolb, 1981-1991 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Lewis, 1980-1982 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Lowenthal, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - Lubis, 1980-1981 (Box R1993)
    - Scholars - MacKenzie, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - McNaught, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - McVey, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Meier, 1981-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Meller, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Meron, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Middleton, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Miller, A.S., 1980-1981, 1983 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Miller, J.H., 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Modelski, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Nagy, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Nichols, N., 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Paarlberg, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Perkins, J., 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Pines, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Reed, J.S., 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Rochlin, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Rummel, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Sahni, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Seers, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Sen, 1979-1983 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Shankar, 1980-1983 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Solow, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Stolley, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Tagliabue, 1980-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Tajfel, 1979-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Targan, 1980-1981 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Terr, 1979-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Treverton, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box R1994)
    - Scholars - Ussachevsky, 1981-1982 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Vorenberg, 1979-1981 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Walsh, J.A., 1980-1981 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Wanshel, 1979-1981 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Warnke, 1979-1982 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Watson, R., 1979-1981 (Box R1995)
      Scope and Contents
      did not go.
    - Scholars - Weitz, 1980-1981 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Weitzman, 1978-1982 (Box R1995)
    - Scholars - Zubrzycki, 1980-1981 (Box R1995)
    - Scientific Concepts of Time - Conference, 1979-1983 (Box R1995)
    - Technical Aids for the Disabled - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R1995)
    - Trade Restrictions - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R1995)
    - U.S. - Soviet Relations in the - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R1995)
    - University and International Value Consensus - Conference, 1978-1982 (Box R1995)
    - World Literature - Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R1995)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - (Social Science & Legal Research on Population Policy) Evaluators (A-Z), 1973-1979 (Box R2012)
    - Inquiries (A-Z), 1971-1975 (Box R2013)
    - Referrals (A-Z), 1977-1978 (Box R2013)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Florida, 211
      - Sly, David F., 1978-1982 (Box R2013)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Massachusetts, 224
      - Aquino, Felix J., 1978-1981 (Box R2013)
      - Rogers, Rosemarie, 1975-1983 (Box R2013)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - New York, 235
      - Min, Kyonghee, 1978-1982 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - North Carolina, 236
      - Aghajanian, Akbar, 1977-1982 (Box R2014)
      - Turchi, Boone A., 1978-1982 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Ohio, 238
      - Kelley, Samuel C., 1979-1982 (Box R2014)
      - Tien, H. Yuan, 1978-1982 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Colombia, 311
      - AMIDEP - Fertility Workshop, 1979-1982 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - England, 401
      - Mauskopf, Josephine, 1979-1981 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Nepal, 474
      - Uprety, Dr. Hari Nandan, 1977-1981 (Box R2014)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Gold Coast, 496
      - Oppong, Christine, 1976-1982 (Box R2015)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Korea, 613
      - Lee, Hyo-Chae, 1977-1982 (Box R2015)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Indonesia, 652
      - Hugo, Graeme John, 1978-1981 (Box R2015)
  - Demographic Evaluation Projects, 151
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - North Carolina, 236
      - University of North Carolina - Demographic Research Consortium, 1979-1982 (Box R2015)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Brazil, 305
      - Population Statistics - Henriques, 1978-1983 (Box R2015)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Nigeria, 497
      - University of Calabar - Uyanga, 1977-1982 (Box R2015)
  - 152
    - 152: Argentina, 301
      - Torcuato di Tella Institute - Latin American Employment, 1971-1979 (Box R2016)
  - CILCA, 165
    - Permanent Interstate Committee for Drought Control in the Sahel, 1980-1982 (Box R2027)
  - 175
    - 175 - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Bacon, Mary Montle, 1979-1983 (Box R2032)
      - Bruce-Novoa, John D., 1979-1981 (Box R2032)
      - Casas, Jesus Manuel, 1980-1981 (Box R2032)
      - Castillo, Pedro, 1980-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Christian, Charles Melvin, 1980-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Combs, Michael W., 1980-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Garcia, Philip, 1979-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr., 1980-1983 (Box R2032)
      - Gavillan Torres, Eva M., 1979-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Harris, R.L., Jr., 1978-1981 (Box R2032)
      - Lozano, Anthony G., 1979-1980 (Box R2032)
      - Matute-Bianchi, Marie Eugenia, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2032)
      - Morse, Roberta Naomi, 1980-1981 (Box R2032)
      - Rabassa, Clemintine Christos, 1978-1980 (Box R2032)
      - Sledge, Linda Mae-Lan-Ching, 1979-1982 (Box R2032)
      - Wong, Yen Lu, 1978-1982 (Box R2033)
      - Wynter, Sylvia, 1980-1982 (Box R2033)
  - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands, 190
    - International Council for Research in Agroforestry (Box R2034)